<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Law360: Class Action</title>
    <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
    <description>Latest articles for: Class Action</description>
    <copyright>Copyright 2015 Portfolio Media, Inc.</copyright>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 16:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>DirecTV Looks To Nix Technicians' 'Cookie Cutter' FLSA Suit</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737255?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737255</guid>
      <description>DirecTV pushed a New Jersey federal judge to toss a putative Fair Labor Standards Act class action from technicians alleging they were shorted pay, maintaining Friday that the group actually comprises independent contractors and not DirecTV employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Supreme Court Refuses To Hear CarMax's Iskanian Challenge</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737422?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737422</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Supreme Court refused Monday to review the California high court's Iskanian decision, which exempts state Private Attorneys General Act claims from mandatory arbitration and which CarMax argued was preempted by federal law and created an unneeded hardship for in-state employers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 16:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>3rd Circ. Denies Rehearing Bid In Google Tracking Suit</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737289?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737289</guid>
      <description>The Third Circuit on Friday refused to review en banc a panel decision affirming the dismissal of claims within multidistrict litigation against Google over its alleged practice of bypassing Internet browser privacy settings to track Internet usage, letting stand a ruling that revived portions of the suit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 15:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>J&amp;J Hit With Class Suit Alleging FCRA Violations </title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737223?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737223</guid>
      <description>Johnson &amp; Johnson and staffing company Kelly Services have been hit with a putative class action accusing them of violating the Fair Credit Reporting Act after rescinding an applicant&amp;rsquo;s job offer based on a criminal conviction found in his consumer report without properly disclosing the report&amp;rsquo;s employment purposes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 15:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>JPMorgan's Junior Mortgage Demands Illegal, Lawsuit Says</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737328?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737328</guid>
      <description>JPMorgan was hit with a proposed class action in California federal court Friday from a borrower claiming it illegally continued to demand payment from mortgage holders on their junior loans after their senior mortgages had been foreclosed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Ethicon Says Bulk Demand For Mesh Records Is 'Burdensome' </title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737488?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737488</guid>
      <description>Johnson &amp; Johnson's Ethicon Inc. on Friday fought a demand by patients in multidistrict litigation over its pelvic repair systems products for records detailing the design and production of various batches of those mesh products, arguing that it would be "inordinately burdensome."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 15:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Divided 2nd Circ. Denies Rehearing In 9/11 Detainee Case</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/736989?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/736989</guid>
      <description>A sharply divided Second Circuit voted Friday not to review a decision that revived claims in a proposed class action accusing high-level law enforcement officials of contributing to the abuse of immigrants who were detained in the wake of 9/11 because they were Arab, Muslim or stereotyped that way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 14:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Calif. Health Club's Youth Discount Upheld In Age Bias Row</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737274?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737274</guid>
      <description>A California fitness club chain was rightly freed from a proposed class action over discounted memberships for adults under 30, a state appeals court ruled Friday, finding the pricing gap was not arbitrary or &amp;ldquo;invidious&amp;rdquo; discrimination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 13:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>GM Falsely Advertised Trucks' Towing Capacity, Suit Says</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737247?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737247</guid>
      <description>General Motors Co. was hit in California federal court Friday with a nationwide putative class action accusing the automaker of hawking two types of pickup trucks that don't live up to their advertised towing capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 13:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>2016 Should Bring Major TCPA Developments</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/735230?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/735230</guid>
      <description>This year ushered in significant developments regarding the Telephone Consumer Protection Act’s application to calls and text messages to mobile phones. What can we expect in 2016? Anna Hsia of ZwillGen PLLC discusses six developments to monitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 10:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>High Court Boosts Federal Arbitration Rule In DirecTV Case</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/733069?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/733069</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday shot down a consumer class action over DirecTV&amp;rsquo;s early termination fees, reversing a California court ruling and signaling to states hostile to arbitration that there is no getting around the federal preference for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 21:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>JPMorgan Says Claims Over $2B Fine Should Stay Dismissed</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/736706?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/736706</guid>
      <description>JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. took a swing at a shareholder's bid to revive its derivative suit accusing the bank's leadership of fiduciary duty breaches that led to $2 billion in fines, saying that the allegations had been rightfully knocked out because the issues had already been decided in another case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 21:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Special Masters Appointed In GM Ignition-Switch Settlement</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737093?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737093</guid>
      <description>A New York federal judge on Friday appointed two Louisiana-based attorneys as special masters to oversee all aspects of a settlement fund agreed to in September by General Motors Co. and a group of drivers in ongoing multidistrict litigation over injuries related to its faulty ignition switches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 20:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Cablevision Settles Long-Running Suit Over Box-Tying</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737201?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737201</guid>
      <description>A putative class of Cablevision subscribers alleging the company used its market muscle to force them into renting its cable boxes asked a federal judge Friday to certify a settlement class and approve a months-long negotiated settlement obligating Cablevision to activate and support third-party boxes, among other requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 20:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>MSG Interns Lose Settlement Approval Bid In OT Suit</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/736782?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/736782</guid>
      <description>A New York federal judge on Thursday refused to approve a proposed settlement in a putative class and collective action in which former unpaid interns for The Madison Square Garden Co. claim that they are owed minimum wages and overtime pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 20:23:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Jimmy John's Workers Can Submit FLSA Statements</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737116?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737116</guid>
      <description>A Fair Labor Standards Act class action filed by a group of Jimmy John&amp;rsquo;s workers who claim they were stiffed on overtime overcame an early challenge when an Illinois federal court on Friday allowed statements from the workers to be admitted as evidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 20:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Uber Drivers Push Court To Block New Arbitration Agreement</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737177?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737177</guid>
      <description>A class of Uber Technologies Inc. drivers on Friday urged a California federal court to bar Uber from rolling out a new arbitration agreement drafted in the wake of a ruling this week saying that the ride-hailing service company's prior agreements are unenforceable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 19:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>Corn Producers Look To Stop Bellwether Strike Motion In MDL</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737035?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737035</guid>
      <description>Corn producers battling Syngenta in multidistrict litigation over genetically modified corn seed that allegedly tainted U.S. exports sought Friday to preemptively fight off an upcoming move by Syngenta to strike some bellwether cases, accusing the company of &amp;ldquo;sandbagging&amp;rdquo; in Kansas federal court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 19:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>BP Hit With Class Action In Mexico Over Deepwater Horizon</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737080?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/737080</guid>
      <description>BP PLC units in Mexico and the U.S. are facing a massive class action that seeks compensation for Mexican residents and businesses harmed by the 2010 Deepwater Horizon oil spill but left out of American settlements, an attorney representing the plaintiffs said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2015 19:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <title>NJ Judge Keeps Fraud Claim In Discolored Decking Suit</title>
      <link>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/736908?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=section</link>
      <guid>http://www.law360.com/classaction/articles/736908</guid>
      <description>A New Jersey federal judge on Thursday refused to cut state law fraud claims from a proposed class action claiming that TimberTech Ltd.&amp;rsquo;s XLM decking products are prone to splotchy discoloration, saying that the consumers adequately suggested unlawful conduct that led to the alleged loss.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
